$dquestl_active	 Active 

; Message
$dquestl_thank_you_for_playing	Quest Lookup: Thank you for playing! 

; Error
$dquestl_quests_are_not_running_new	One of Quest Lookup's quests hasn't started. It's okay, you can save and reload to try again. This may be due to the Papyrus engine being under too heavy a load.
$dquestl_quests_are_not_running_load	One of Quest Lookup's quests is not running. Try to reload, else you may need to reinstall the mod. Please do not stop any Quest Lookup quests in the console.
